A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 100 International - Series 253 Washington FA387a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1929-1977; 200; 113 box(es)
  - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1929-1973; 200.E; 4 box(es)
    - Social Science Research Council - Supplemental Material, 1951-1958; 12 Items (Box 255, Folder 2468)
    - Social Science Research Council - Directory, 1950-1952 (Box 255, Folder 2469)
    - Social Science Research Council - Legal and Political Philosophy, 1953-1967 (Box 255, Folder 2470)
    - Social Science Research Council - Legal and Political Philosophy, 1953-1967 (Box 255, Folder 2471)
    - Social Science Research Council - Legal and Political Philosophy, 1953-1967 (Box 255, Folder 2472)
    - Tsai, Albert Y.M. - (Fellowship, Reproductive Biology), 1972-1973 (Box 255, Folder 2473)
    - Vandenberg, Gary - (Fellowship, Reproductive Biology), 1971-1973 (Box 255, Folder 2474)
    - National Research Council - List of Postdoctoral Fellowships, 1950 (Box 617, Folder 5303)
    - National Research Council - List of Awards, 1953 (Box 617, Folder 5304)
  - United States - Humanities Fellows, 1948; 200.ER; 1 folder(s)
    - Hamilton, Thomas H. - (Bibliography for Financing Higher Education), 1948 (Box 255, Folder 2475)
  - United States - Declinations, 1960-1968; 200.F; 0.4 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.4 cubic feet
    Four folders, three of which deal with the Asia Foundation, 1968.
    - Asia Foundation, 1968-1972 (Box 255, Folder 2476)
    - Asia Foundation - Supplemental Material - (Background Papers), 1968 (Box 256, Folder 2477)
      Related Archival Materials note
      see also folder 2476.
    - Asia Foundation - Supplemental Material - (Proposed Budget), 1968 (Box 256, Folder 2478)
    - Tulane University - Medical School - (Proposed Extension), 1960-1962 (Box 256, Folder 2479)
  - United States - Public Health Services, 1955-1962; 200.K; 0.2 Cubic Feet; 0.5 __Box __0.2 cubic feet
    2 folders dealing with grants to Harvard University
    - Harvard University - Burden, Robert P. - (Sanitary Engineering Teaching), 1961-1962 (Box 256, Folder 2480)
    - Harvard University - Thomas, Harold A. - (Travel Grant, Europe and Latin America), 1955-1959 (Box 256, Folder 2481)
  - United States - Public Health Demonstrations, 1951-1956; 200.L; 0.2 Cubic Feet; 0.5 __Box __0.2 cubic feet
    2 folders of material, one dealing with Harvard University, the other with the University of Michigan.
    - Harvard University - Rice, Elizabeth P. - (Public Health Programs) - (Travel Grant, Europe), 1956 (Box 256, Folder 2482)
    - University of Michigan - Public Health Economics - (Field Study, Canadian Public Health Services), 1951-1955 (Box 256, Folder 2483)
  - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1947-1979; 200.R; 88 Cubic Feet; 220 __Boxes __88 cubic feet
    - Abell, Marcelle A. - (Aesthetics, Manuscript Preparation), 1957 (Box 256, Folder 2484)
    - Abraham Lincoln Association - (Lincoln Papers Publication), 1947-1954 (Box 256, Folder 2485)
    - Abraham Lincoln Association - (Lincoln Papers Publication), 1947-1954 (Box 256, Folder 2486)
    - Academy of American Franciscan History - Religious History of the Americas - (Conference), 1956-1957 (Box 256, Folder 2487)
    - Academy of American Franciscan History - Religious History of the Americas - (Conference), 1958 (Box 257, Folder 2488)
    - Academy of American Poets - (Kray, Elizabeth) - (Readings Program), 1962-1966 (Box 257, Folder 2489)
    - Academy of American Poets - Public School Program, 1965-1972 (Box 257, Folder 2490)
    - Academy of American Poets - Public School Program, 1965-1972 (Box 257, Folder 2491)
    - Academy of American Poets - Public School Program, 1965-1972 (Box 257, Folder 2492)
    - Academy of American Poets - Public School Program, 1965-1972 (Box 257, Folder 2493)
    - Academy of American Poets - Public School Program, 1965-1972 (Box 257, Folder 2494)
    - Actors Studio, Inc. - (Playwriting Program), 1960-1962 (Box 257, Folder 2495)
    - Actors Studio, Inc. - (Playwriting Program), 1963-1964 (Box 258, Folder 2496)
    - Actors Studio, Inc. - (Playwriting Program), 1963-1964 (Box 258, Folder 2497)
    - Actors Theatre of Louisville - (General Support), 1964-1966 (Box 258, Folder 2498)
    - Actors Theatre of Louisville - (General Support), 1964-1966 (Box 258, Folder 2499)
    - Actors Theatre of Louisville - (General Support) - Supplemental Material, 1965-1966 (Box 258, Folder 2500)
    - African-American Institute, Inc. - Journalism - (Travel Grants, Africa), 1963-1965 (Box 258, Folder 2501)
    - Afro-American Total Theatre Arts Foundation, Inc. - (Playwriting Program), 1969-1971 (Box 258, Folder 2502)
    - Ailey American Dance Theatre, 1968-1969 (Box 259, Folder 2503)
    - Alaska Festival of Music, 1964-1966 (Box 259, Folder 2504)
    - Albarwild Theatre Arts, Inc. - (Playwright's Unit), 1965-1971 (Box 259, Folder 2505)
    - Albarwild Theatre Arts, Inc. - (Playwright's Unit), 1965-1971 (Box 259, Folder 2506)
    - Alexander, Ross, 1967-1971 (Box 259, Folder 2507)
    - Allen, Donald M. - (Travel Grant, Latin America), 1958-1960 (Box 259, Folder 2508)
    - American Council on Education - Japanese Student Counseling - (Training Program), 1952-1954 (Box 259, Folder 2509)
    - American Council on Education - Japanese Student Counseling - (Training Program), 1955 (Box 260, Folder 2510)
    - American Council on Education - Textbook Revision Study - (Quillen, James H.), 1947-1951 (Box 260, Folder 2511)
    - American Council for Emigres in the Professions, Inc. - Domjan, Jozsef - (Refugee, Artist), 1957-1963 (Box 260, Folder 2512)
    - American Council for Emigres in the Professions, Inc. - Domjan, Jozsef - (Refugee, Artist), 1957-1963 (Box 260, Folder 2513)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Area Studies - Leonard, Irving A. - (Travel Grant, Great Britain), 1951-1953 (Box 260, Folder 2514)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Chinese History - (Hu Shih), 1942-1945 (Box 260, Folder 2515)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Chinese History - Committee Meetings, 1962-1965 (Box 260, Folder 2516)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Chinese Thought Conference - (Villa Serbelloni), 1969-1970, 1976 (Box 260, Folder 2517)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Congress of Orientalists, 1959-1961 (Box 260, Folder 2518)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Congress of Orientalists, 1959-1961 (Box 260, Folder 2519)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Encyclopedia of Islam, 1949-1964 (Box 261, Folder 2520)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Encyclopedia of Islam, 1949-1964 (Box 261, Folder 2521)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Federal Arts Projects, 1942-1953 (Box 261, Folder 2522)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Federal Arts Projects, 1942-1953 (Box 261, Folder 2523)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Federal Arts Projects - (Reports), 1943; 3 Items (Box 261, Folder 2524)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, 1944-April 1946 (Box 261, Folder 2525)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, 1944-April 1946 (Box 261, Folder 2526)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, 1944-April 1946 (Box 261, Folder 2527)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2528)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2529)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2530)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2531)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2532)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2533)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2534)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, May 1946-February 1950 (Box 262, Folder 2535)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, March 1950-1955 (Box 263, Folder 2536)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, March 1950-1955 (Box 263, Folder 2537)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, March 1950-1955 (Box 263, Folder 2538)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, March 1950-1955 (Box 263, Folder 2539)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - General Support, March 1950-1955 (Box 263, Folder 2540)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Germanic Studies - (Goethe Bicentennial Conference), 1948-1950 (Box 263, Folder 2541)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Graves, Mortimer - (Travel Grant, Great Britain), 1947-1950 (Box 263, Folder 2542)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - History Conference - (Uniformities in History), 1949-1954 (Box 263, Folder 2543)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - History Conference - (Uniformities in History) - Reports, 1949-1950; 6 Items (Box 264, Folder 2544)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Junior Humanities Personnel, 1951-1952 (Box 264, Folder 2545)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Junior Humanities Personnel, 1951-1952 (Box 264, Folder 2546)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Junior Humanities Personnel, 1951-1952 (Box 264, Folder 2547)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Korean Studies, 1947-1950, 1955 (Box 264, Folder 2548)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Mongolian Studies, 1948-1951 (Box 264, Folder 2549)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Near East Studies, 1947 (Box 264, Folder 2550)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Near East Studies, 1948-1955 (Box 265, Folder 2551)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Near East Studies, 1948-1955 (Box 265, Folder 2552)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Near East Studies, 1948-1955 (Box 265, Folder 2553)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Near East Studies, 1948-1955 (Box 265, Folder 2554)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Near East Studies, 1948-1955 (Box 265, Folder 2555)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Near East Studies, 1948-1955 (Box 265, Folder 2556)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Odegaard, Charles E. - (Travel Grant, Great Britain), 1951 (Box 265, Folder 2557)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Pacific Coast Committee, 1942-1945 (Box 265, Folder 2558)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Pacific Coast Committee, 1946-1954 (Box 266, Folder 2559)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Pacific Coast Committee, 1946-1954 (Box 266, Folder 2560)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Personnel in the Humanities, 1948-1956 (Box 266, Folder 2561)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Personnel in the Humanities, 1948-1956 (Box 266, Folder 2562)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Personnel in the Humanities, 1948-1956 (Box 266, Folder 2563)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Personnel in the Humanities, 1948-1956 (Box 266, Folder 2564)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Personnel in the Humanities - Reports, 1953-1954; 2 Items (Box 266, Folder 2565)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Schilpp, Paul A. - (Travel Grant, Germany), 1947-1950, 1955-1956 (Box 267, Folder 2566)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Slavic Studies, 1943-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2567)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Slavic Studies, 1943-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2568)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Slavic Studies, 1943-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2569)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Slavic Studies, 1943-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2570)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Slavic Studies, 1943-1957 (Box 267, Folder 2571)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Southern Regional Conference, 1946-1951, 1955 (Box 268, Folder 2572)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Southern Regional Conference, 1946-1951, 1955 (Box 268, Folder 2573)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Summer Institutes - Linguistics, 1956-1957 (Box 268, Folder 2574)
    - American Council of Learned Societies - Taoism Conference, 1957-1968, 1970 (Box 268, Folder 2575)
    - American Craftsmen's Council, 1958-1965 (Box 268, Folder 2576)
    - American Craftsmen's Council, 1958-1965 (Box 268, Folder 2577)
    - American Dance Theatre - (Lincoln Center), 1965-1966 (Box 268, Folder 2578)
    - American Dance Theatre - (Lincoln Center), 1964-1965 (Box 269, Folder 2579)
    - American Educational Theatre Association - Latin American Drama - (Productions in the United States), 1960-1962 (Box 269, Folder 2580)
    - American Educational Theatre Association - Latin American Drama - (Productions in the United States), 1960-1962 (Box 269, Folder 2581)
    - American Educational Theatre Association - Latin American Drama - (Vodanovic, Sergio, "Let the Dogs Bark" script), 1961 (Box 269, Folder 2582)
    - American Historical Association - Films, 1967-1969, 1970-1972 (Box 269, Folder 2583)
    - American Historical Association - Guide to Historical Literature, 1955-1961 (Box 269, Folder 2584)
    - American Historical Association - Guide to Historical Literature, 1955-1961 (Box 269, Folder 2585)
    - American Historical Association - South Asian History - (Visiting Professorships), 1955-June 1956 (Box 269, Folder 2586)
    - American Historical Society - South Asian History - (Visiting Professorships), July 1956-1965 (Box 270, Folder 2587)
    - American Historical Society - South Asian History - (Visiting Professorships), July 1956-1965 (Box 270, Folder 2588)
    - American Historical Society - South Asian History - (Visiting Professorships), July 1956-1965 (Box 270, Folder 2589)
    - American International Music Fund - (Recordings), 1957-1961, 1964 (Box 270, Folder 2590)
    - American International Music Fund - (Recordings), 1957-1961, 1964 (Box 270, Folder 2591)
    - American International Music Fund - (Recordings), 1957-1961, 1964 (Box 270, Folder 2592)
    - American International Music Fund - Reports, 1956-1957, 1959; 3 Items (Box 271, Folder 2593)
    - American Library Association - Bibliographical Guide, 1948-1951 (Box 271, Folder 2594)
    - American Library Association - British Librarians' Visit, 1963-1964 (Box 271, Folder 2595)
    - American Library Association - Guide to Comparative Literature, 1942-1951, 1956 (Box 271, Folder 2596)
    - American Library Association - Guide to Comparative Literature, 1942-1951, 1956 (Box 271, Folder 2597)
    - American Library Association - Indian Librarian Training, 1958-1962 (Box 271, Folder 2598)
    - American Library Association - Japanese Librarian Training, 1958-1960, 1962 (Box 271, Folder 2599)
    - American Library Association - Overseas Library Development, 1955-1958 (Box 271, Folder 2600)
    - American Library Association - Overseas Library Development, 1955-1958 (Box 271, Folder 2601)
    - American Library Association - Overseas Library Development, 1959-1968 (Box 272, Folder 2602)
    - American Library Association - Overseas Library Development, 1959-1968 (Box 272, Folder 2603)
    - American Library Association - Overseas Library Development, 1959-1968 (Box 272, Folder 2604)
    - American Library Association - Overseas Library Development, 1959-1968 (Box 272, Folder 2605)
    - American Library Association - Overseas Library Development, 1959-1968 (Box 272, Folder 2606)
    - American Library Association - Soviet Exchange, 1959-1963, 1966 (Box 272, Folder 2607)
    - American Literary History - (Robert E. Spiller, Willard Thorp), 1939-1944 (Box 272, Folder 2608)
    - American Literary History - (Robert E. Spiller, Willard Thorp), 1939-1944 (Box 272, Folder 2609)
    - American Literary History - (Robert E. Spiller, Willard Thorp), 1945-1949, 1954-1955 (Box 273, Folder 2610)
    - American Music Center - Manual (of information), 1949-1950, 1952, 1954, 1958 (Box 273, Folder 2611)
    - American Music Center - Turkish Music Libraries, 1955-1956 (Box 273, Folder 2612)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - (Experimental Theatre), 1946-1949 (Box 273, Folder 2613)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - (Experimental Theatre), 1946-1949 (Box 273, Folder 2614)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Arena Theatre Study - (Mangum, Edward), 1954-1958 (Box 273, Folder 2615)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Hungarian Refugees, 1956-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2616)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Hungarian Refugees - Benzce, Miklos, 1957-1958 (Box 274, Folder 2617)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Hungarian Refugees - Darazs, Arpad, 1957-1958 (Box 274, Folder 2618)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Hungarian Refugees - Hontvary, Michael, 1957-1958 (Box 274, Folder 2619)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Hungarian Refugees - Majorossy, Aladar, 1957-1958, 1961 (Box 274, Folder 2620)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Hungarian Refugees - Szabo, Sandor, 1956-1961 (Box 274, Folder 2621)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Mandelbaum, Alan - (Audience Survey), 1950-1951 (Box 274, Folder 2622)
    - American National Theatre and Academy - Mandelbaum, Alan - "The Guests of The Cocktail Party: A Study of Mr. Eliot's Audience" - ANTA - MAN, 1951 (Box 274, Folder 2623)
    - American Numismatic Society - (Miles, George C.) - (Travel Grant, Near East), 1962-1964 (Box 274, Folder 2624)
    - American Personnel and Guidance Association, Inc. - Japanese Student Counseling, 1956-1957 (Box 274, Folder 2625)
    - American Philosophical Association - (Eastern Division) - Conference Materials, 1952-1955 (Box 274, Folder 2626)
    - American Philosophical Association - Latin American Philosophers - (Travel Grants, United States), 1946-1950 (Box 274, Folder 2627)
    - American Philosophical Association - Latin American Philosophers - (Travel Grants, United States), 1951-1954 (Box 275, Folder 2628)
    - American Philosophical Association - Oriental Philosophy - (Harris, Frederick P.), 1953-1955 (Box 275, Folder 2629)
    - American Philosophical Association - Public Interest Study - (Leys, Wayne A.R.), 1958-1959 (Box 275, Folder 2630)
    - American Philosophical Association - Western Division - (Social and Political Philosphy), 1952-1959, 1961-1962 (Box 275, Folder 2631)
    - American Philosophical Association - Western Division - (Social and Political Philosphy), 1952-1959, 1961-1962 (Box 275, Folder 2632)
    - American Philosophical Association - Western Division - (Social and Political Philosphy), 1952-1959, 1961-1962 (Box 275, Folder 2633)
    - American Place Theatre - (General Support), 1962-1971 (Box 276, Folder 2634)
    - American Place Theatre - (General Support), 1962-1971 (Box 276, Folder 2635)
    - American Place Theatre - (General Support), 1962-1971 (Box 276, Folder 2636)
    - American Place Theatre - (General Support), 1962-1971 (Box 276, Folder 2637)
    - American Place Theatre - Handman, Wynn - (Travel Grant, Europe and Near East), 1966 (Box 276, Folder 2638)
    - American Press Institute - Foreign Press Personnel - (Columbia University) - (Travel Grants, United States), 1954-1966 (Box 277, Folder 2639)
    - American Press Institute - Foreign Press Personnel - (Columbia University) - (Travel Grants, United States), 1954-1966 (Box 277, Folder 2640)
    - American Press Institute - Foreign Press Personnel - (Columbia University) - (Travel Grants, United States), 1954-1966 (Box 277, Folder 2641)
    - American Press Institute - Foreign Press Personnel - (Columbia University) - (Travel Grants, United States), 1954-1966 (Box 277, Folder 2642)
    - American Publication Exports - (Wessells, Helen) - Survey, 1951-1952 (Box 277, Folder 2643)
    - American Puppet Arts Council - (Bil Baird Theatre), August-September 1967 (Box 277, Folder 2644)
    - American Puppet Arts Council - (Bil Baird Theatre), October 1967-1970 (Box 278, Folder 2645)
    - American Shakespeare Festival - (Stratford, Connecticut) - (General Support), 1951-1960 (Box 278, Folder 2646)
    - American Shakespeare Festival - (Stratford, Connecticut) - (General Support), 1951-1960 (Box 278, Folder 2647)
    - American Shakespeare Festival - (Stratford, Connecticut) - (General Support), 1951-1960 (Box 278, Folder 2648)
    - American Shakespeare Festival - (Stratford, Connecticut) - (General Support), 1951-1960 (Box 278, Folder 2649)
    - American Shakespeare Festival - (Stratford, Connecticut) - (General Support), 1951-1960 (Box 278, Folder 2650)
    - American Shakespeare Festival - Dramatic Education - (St. Denis, Michel), 1958-1959, 1961 (Box 279, Folder 2651)
    - American Slavic and East European Review - (General Support), 1946-1951 (Box 279, Folder 2652)
    - American Slavic and East European Review - (General Support), 1946-1951 (Box 279, Folder 2653)
    - American Studies Association - (Conferences), 1951-1953 (Box 279, Folder 2654)
    - American Studies Association -Fugitive Conference - (Southern Literary Movement), 1955-1959 (Box 279, Folder 2655)
    - American Symphony Orchestra - (Charles Ives Fourth Symphony Performance) - (Stokowski, Leopold), 1964-1966 (Box 279, Folder 2656)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), 1953-March 1954 (Box 279, Folder 2657)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), March 1954-September 1956 (Box 280, Folder 2658)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), March 1954-September 1956 (Box 280, Folder 2659)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), March 1954-September 1956 (Box 280, Folder 2660)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), March 1954-September 1956 (Box 280, Folder 2661)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), March 1954-September 1956 (Box 280, Folder 2662)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), March 1954-September 1956 (Box 280, Folder 2663)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), March 1954-September 1956 (Box 280, Folder 2664)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), September 1956-April 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2665)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), September 1956-April 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2666)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), September 1956-April 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2667)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), September 1956-April 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2668)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), September 1956-April 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2669)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), September 1956-April 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2670)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), September 1956-April 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2671)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), April 1959-1962 (Box 282, Folder 2672)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), April 1959-1962 (Box 282, Folder 2673)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), April 1959-1962 (Box 282, Folder 2674)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), April 1959-1962 (Box 282, Folder 2675)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), April 1959-1962 (Box 282, Folder 2676)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), April 1959-1962 (Box 282, Folder 2677)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League - (General Support), 1963-1968 (Box 283, Folder 2678)